Guide to the Public Art Fund Archive 1966-2009 MSS.270
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XV: Printed Material, 1963-2008; 7 Linear Feet in 7 record cartons.
  - Statens Konstrad. Byggnadsintegrerad Konst Pa Kemiska Ovningslaboratoriet, Stockholms Universitet, Frescati, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Statens Konstrad. Columna, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Statens Konstrad. Gestaltning, av broplan, molndal, 2000 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Statens Konstrad. Maaria Wirkkala: Forskarcellerna, 2001 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Statens Konstrad. Partner sokes., undated (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Storm King Art Center. Mia Westerlund Roosen: Sculpture and Drawings, 1994 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - The Tel Aviv Museum. Myth Transformed: Painting and Monumental Sculpture of Menashe Kadishman, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Third Eye Centre. Thomas Lawson, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - TSWA 3D, undated (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Tyler Galleries. Jerry Kearns: Deep Cover: The Deadly Art of Illusion, 1991 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - University of California, Irvine, Fine Arts Gallery. James Ford: A Survey, 1980-1983 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - University Gallery, University of Massachusetts at Amherst. Jeffrey Brosk, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation. Aesthetics in Transportation, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Vancouver Association for Noncommercial Culture. Adverse Practises, undated (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - Vancouver Association for Noncommercial Culture. Urban Subjects, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Van der Marck, Jan. Arman, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Vassar College Art Gallery. Patsy Norvell, 1979 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - The Venice Biennale '90/The Israeli Pavilion. Dorchin, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Vermont International Sculpture Symposium, 1973 (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - Victoria Munroe Gallery. Christopher Hewat: Sculpture, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts/Richmond. Installations, 1986 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Visual Arts Program, National Endowment for the Arts. Insights/On Sites, 1984 (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - Walter/Mcbean Gallery, San Francisco Art Institute. Joyce J. Scott: Images Concealed, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 28)
  - Wave Hill Sculpture Garden. Figure in the Landscape, 1978 (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - Weatherspoon Art Gallery. Ronald Bladen: Drawings and Sculptural Models, 1995 (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art. Another Chance for Cities, 1970 (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art. Contemporary American Sculpture: 1970 Annual Exhibition (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art. Developments in Recent Sculpture, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art at Equitable Center. Video Art: Expanded Forms, 1988 (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - Wildenstein. Rhonda Roland Shearer: Ambiguous Figures, New Bronze Works, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 35)
  - Yorkshire Sculpture Park/The Nelson-Atkins Museum of Art/The Indianapolis Museum of Art. Ursula von Rydingsvard, 1997 (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - Zabriskie Gallery. Stuart Davis: Murals, 1976 (Box 139, Folder 37)
- Oversize Series I: City Walls, 200970
  This series contains original mock-ups of mural designs created on canvas by multiple artists during the City Walls program.
  - City Walls Canvas - Milicevic, Tania (Mercer & 3rd) - 1970 - 1 of 2, cuid5975; 199990; 1 item one painting; 100.5 x 43 inches. (Box 113)
    Artist: Tania Milicevic
    Paintings (visual works)
  - City Walls Canvas - Milicevic, Tania (Mercer & 3rd) - 1970 - 2 of 2, 201065; 100.5 x 43 inches. (Roll-storage R1)
  - City Walls Canvas - Pekarsky, Mel- (Bleecker and Lafayette) 1970, 201058; 96 x 49 inches. (Roll-storage R1)
  - City Walls Canvas - Williams, Todd - (Livingston & Bond) - 1970, 199991; 49 x 58 inches. (Roll-storage R1)
  - City Walls - New York Times Poster (Newsprint), 1970; 200991 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- Oversize Series II: Public Arts Council, 200990
  This series contains posters and site plans pertaining to projects of the Public Arts Council.
  - New York Professional Women Artists: Walk Through Art (Exhibition Poster), 1974; 200922 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Tumarkin, Igael - PAC [Public Arts Council] Project Site Plans, 1976; 200924 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Valinski, Dennis - "At Waterside" - Poster, 1976; 200923 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - "Yield Brother" Posters, 1971-1972 (Folder 12)
- Oversize Series VI: Project Files, 179243
  This series contains oversize material pertaining to projects of the Public Art Fund, including site plans, original drawings, signs, and posters. Notable objects include sixteen original signs from Martin Wong's "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired", completed in 1990, and an original poster for Agnes Denes "Wheatfield" (1982).
  - Torffield, Marvin - "Volume" Poster, 1980; 200926 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Wendkos, Gina, 1980; 200925 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Wells, David - Central Park Site Plan, 1981; 200928 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Finkel, Alan - "View for the Catenary Curve Empire" - Fulton Ferry State Park - Site Plan, 1981; 200927 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Denes, Agnes - "Wheatfield" Poster, 1982; 200929 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - The Bridges Show - poster, 1983; 200930 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Aprile, Tom - "Family Room With a View" - site plan, 1984; 200931 (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Rothfarb, Ed - Proposal - Walt Whitman Park - site plans, 1984; 200932 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Chin, Mel - site plan, 1984; 200933 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Aycock, Alice - Doris Freedman Plaza site plans, 1986; 200936 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Elrod, Biff - Site Plan - 1 of 2, 1986; 200934 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Elrod, Biff - Site Plan - 2 of 2, 1986; 200996 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Red Spot Outdoor Slide Theater, [1986]; 200935 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Artschwager, Richard - 2 site plans, 1987; 200937 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - "Newsstand 88" - poster for submissions, 1988; 200939 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Schafer, David - poster, 1988; 200938 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Dwyer, Nancy - "Get you there for sure" - Transit posters, 1989; 199976; 36 x 10 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Dwyer, Nancy - "Transit Gets You There" (subway ad), 1989; 200940 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Gaskins, Franco "The Great", 1989; 200941 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Gianakos, Steve - Bronx Zoo - Transit Posters, 1989; 199977; 45 x 30 inches. (Roll-storage R9)
  - Gianakos, Steve - Bronx Zoo - Transit Poster, 1989; 215624 (Folder 12)
  - Fulbrecht, William - "Bill of Rights" - Site Plans, 1990; 200981 (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Video Drive-in poster, 1990; 200942 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - Stop, 1990; cuid6048; 199978; 5 items five signs; 29.5 x 30 inches. (Box 127, Item MSS.270.cuid6048)
    Direction signs.; Works of art.
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - School for the Deaf, 1990; cuid6049; 201069; 4 items four signs; 29.5 x 30 inches. (Item MSS.270.cuid6049)
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - One Way, 1990; cuid6050; 201077; 4 items four signs; 35.5 x 12 inches. (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6050)
  - Wong, Martin - "Traffic Signs for the Hearing Impaired" - Yellow People Crossing, 1990; cuid6051; 201081; 3 items three signs; 29.5 x 30 inches. (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6051)
  - Gran Fury, "Spanish" - "Simplemente Muren" "Women Don't get AIDS they just die from it"- Bus Shelter Poster - 1 of 2, 1991; 199979; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R4)
  - Gran Fury, "Spanish" - "Simplemente Muren" "Women Don't get AIDS they just die from it"- Bus Shelter Poster - 2 of 2, 1991; 199980; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R4)
  - Guerrilla Girls - "First they take away a woman's right to choose, now they're censoring art", 1991; cuid6040; 199981; 1 item one mural composed of 10 posters (Box 129)
    Posters.
  - Kruger "Help" - Bus shelter poster, 1991; 199982; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R4)
  - Ressler, Robert - "Mantis" - Site plan, 1991; 200944 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Ressler, Robert - Columbus Park: "Mantis" - Proposal, 1991; 200945 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Rockburne, Dorthea - "Vary form, Curve" + "Ship Curves", 1991; 200982 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 1 of 4, 1992; 199983; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage R4)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 2 of 4, 1992; 201059; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage R4)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 3 of 4, 1992; 201060; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage R4)
  - Allen, Jules - Bus Shelter poster - 4 of 4, 1992; 201061; 48 x 68 inches. (Roll-storage R4)
  - Deon, Richard - "Hike New York/Long Island City" - Hand-painted sign, 1992; 199993 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    Description: Richard Long - "Hike New York" hand-painted sign Media: Paper mounted in plastic with tape Dimensions: 23.5 x 16.5 inches
  - Deon, Richard - Hike New York - Long Island City, 1992; cuid6052; 201086; 1 item one sign (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6052)
  - Deon, Richard - Hike New York - Long Island City -- Museum of the Moving Image .3 mi, 1992; cuid6053; 200009; 1 item one sign (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6053)
  - Deon, Richard - Hike New York - Long Island City -- Sunnyside Historic District .5 mi, Thompson Hill Park .8 mi, Thalia Spanish Theatre .8 mi, 1992; cuid6054; 201106 (Box 126, Item MSS.270.cuid6054)
  - Trans-Voices/Blain, Dominique - "US Nickel, Discontinued in 1938", 1992; 199986; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Trans-Voices/Boltanski, Christian - "Avis de Recherche/Notice", 1992; 199985; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Trans-Voices/Cazal, Philippe - "Empire" English, 1992; 200008; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Trans-Voices/Ennadre, Touhami - "Mains du Monde", 1992; 200004; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Trans-Voices/Gerz, Jochen -"Comment Vivre/How to Live", 1992; 200006; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Trans-Voices/Jaar, Alfredo - "1992", 199984; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Trans-Voices/Lafontaine, Marie-Jo - "Nous sommes tous des ombres/We are all shadows" [English], 1992; 199989; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Trans-Voices/Lafontaine, Marie-Jo - "Nous sommes tous des ombres/We are all shadows" [French] (Rolled), 1992; 200972; 60 x 46 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Trans-Voices/Messager, Annette - "Prude America, France Impertinente", 1992; 200007; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Trans-Voices/Simmons, Laurie - "Lying Objects", 1992; 200005; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Trans-Voices/Simpson, Lorna - "Untitled", 1992; 200002; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Trans-Voices/Teraoka, Masami - "AIDS World Story", 1992; 200003; 60 x 46 inches. (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Trans-Voices/Gerz, Jochen [French] (Rolled), 1992; 199987; 60 x 46 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Botero, Fernando - Poster, 1993; 197009; 30 x 45 inches. (Roll-storage R9)
  - Otterness, Tom - Site Plans, 1995; 200946 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Otterness, Tom - Transit Ad (Rolled), 1995; 201070; 11 x 70 inches. (Roll-storage R8)
  - Gonzalez, Maria Elena: Magic Carpet, 1999; 200947 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - LeWitt, Sol - Embassy Suites Wall - site plan, 2000; 200948 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Long, Richard - Transit poster (Rolled) - 1 of 2, 2000; 200010 (Roll-storage R8)
  - Long, Richard - Transit poster (Rolled) - 2 of 2, 2000; 201071 (Roll-storage R8)
  - Otterness, Tom - Hilton Hotel - site plans (4 copies), 2000; 201057 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Westphalen, Olav - "E.S.U.S. Extremely Site Unspecific Sculpture" - Brochure, 2000; 200950 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Goldsworthy, Andy: Museum of Jewish Heritage, 2003; 200959 (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Williams, Clara - "The Price" -site plan, 2003; 200952 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Kentridge, William - "9 Drawings for Projection" - Posters, 2004; 200983 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - West, Franz: "Recent Sculptures" - 2 Posters, 2004; 199999; 20 x 35 inches. (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Aoshima, Chiho - "City Glow" - 2005/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters, 200955 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Kawashima, Hideaki -"Fire" - 2004/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters, 2005; 200954 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Rubins, Nancy - "Placement of Truss", 2005; 200958 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Takano, Aya - "A Night Walk - The Pink Walk Emerges" - 2005/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters, 200956 (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Tsubaki, Noboru - "Aesthetic Pollution" - 1991/ "Little Boy" - 2 posters, 2005; 200953 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Yamada, James - Proposals for "In the Public Realm", 2005; 200984 (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Morris, Sarah - "Robert Towne - [Los Angeles]" - Drawing, 2006; 200957 (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Rubins, Nancy - Site Plan, 2006; 200997 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - "The World is Round" - Poster, 2006-2007; 200985 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Shaun - "Wet Behind the Ear" bus shelter poster, 2008; 199998; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Alison Fleming bus shelter poster, 2008; 199994; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Brian Wengrf Skyx bus shelter poster, 2008; 199995; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Eric + Nadine bus shelter poster, 2008; 199996; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - Fatimah Tuggar - "Transient Transfer" / Poalo + Jason Pine bus shelter poster, 2008; 199997; 48 x 69 inches. (Roll-storage R7)
  - "Griggs" [Yuma Project] - plans and drawings, undated; 200986 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Sonfist, Alan - watercolor, undated; 199992; 30 x 33 inches. (Roll-storage R10)
- Oversize Series VII: Press, Publications, and Promotional Material, 200980
  This series contains two oversize clear mock-ups of a Public Art Fund publication.
  - Public Art Fund Book Plates - 1 of 2, undated; 200987 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Public Art Fund Book Plates - 2 of 2, undated; 200988 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- Oversize Series IX: Photographic Material, 200971
  Arranged chronologically, this series contains oversize photographic material pertaining to projects of the Public Art Fund.
  - "Ebbets Field at the Word Trade Center 1979" - [Brusk], 199975 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Witz, Dan - "Sticks" Photographs, 1998; 200989 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Beecroft, Vanessa - Photograph, 2000; 200974 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Moore, Andrew - Photographs of City Hall, 2001; 200975 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Rawanchaikul, Navin - "I Love Taxi" - Mounted photograph, 2001; 200976; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Alÿs, Francis - "The Modern Procession" - Photographs, 2002; 200977 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Mori, Mariko - "Wave UFO" - Photographs, 2005; 200978 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Brosk, Jeffrey Owen - "Ebbets Field" - Mounted image, undated; 201816; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - DiSuvero, Mark - Mounted Image, undated; 200156 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Dubuffet, Jean -"La Chiffoniere" - Mounted image, undated; 200157; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - General Project Images - Doris Freedman Plaza, undated; 200979 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Johnson, Jerry - "Oceana" - Mounted image, undated; 200152; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Katz, Alex - "Nine Women" - Mounted image - 1 of 2, undated; 200153; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Katz, Alex - "Nine Women" - Mounted image - 2 of 2, undated; 200154; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Martin, Knox - "Venus" - Mounted image, undated; 200148; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Noguchi, Isamu - Mounted image, undated; 200159; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Serra, Richard - Mounted image, undated; 200155; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - [Smith, Tony] - Mounted image, undated; 201817; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified project - Mounted image, undated; 200160; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Wells, David - "Megagleaners on a Field Storefront Blue Chairs" - Mounted image, undated; 200158; 16 x 24 inches. (Box 120, Folder 6)